

ABRAHAM MOISES HUACCHILLO CASTILLO

I am a graduate in Business Administration from the University of Piura with experience in the service industry. I consider myself organized, disciplined, adaptable, and a team player. Currently, I am focused on honing my web development skills through personal and group projects. I have completed practical courses in Docker, GIT and GITHUB, HTML, CSS, React JS, and Go Backend Development, and I am excited to apply these skills in a work environment and continue learning and growing in the field of web development.

21 de diciembre de 1999

+51 992487774

huacchillocastillo@gmail.com

0

Piura - Peru

github.com/Jarbram

IDIOM

Spanish: Native

English: Upper Intermediate

Centro de Idiomas Universidad de Piura (2018 -

2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

SERVICE STAFF CHILIS - PIURA (January 2018 - January 2019)Customer service and food preparation at Chilis restaurant.

SERVICE AREA MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT CHILIS - PIURA (January 2019 - April 2021) Assistant to the management team. Collaborated with store manager and leaders to improve operational efficiency and trained new employees.

BARTENDER CHILIS-PIURA (August 2021 - June 2022) Prepared and served drinks at the bar in Chilis. Managed inventory and maintained bar hygiene and safety standards.

Kitchen Worker, The Lodge Casino (December 2022 - March 2023) Member of the kitchen team at The Lodge Casino in the USA. Assisted with food and beverage preparation and improved English language skills.

Freelance projects with local companies
Developed personal web projects using ReactJS,
MongoDB,PostgreSQL and GO to enhance
Fullstack Developer skills. Collaborated with other
developers on team projects.

EDUCATION

SCHOOL SAN IGNACIO DE LOYOLA PIURA

(2006 - 2016)

UNIVERSIDAD DE PIURA

(2017 - 2022)

Business Administration

PLATZI

(2021 - August 2022)

- Docker Course
- GO Backend Development Course
- GIT and GITHUB Professional Course
- Terminal and Command Line Course
- Database Fundamentals Course
- Linux Server Administration Course
- Practical Go Course: Creating a web server
- Advanced Go Course: Concurrency and Design Patterns
- Definitive course HTML and CSS
- React is

ALURA

(December 2022 - at the moment)
Program ONE with Alura, **Frontend specialization**